Oh my gosh..
What's wrong??? Oh my gosh!!!?
What's wrong???
Y i Xi! Ayden Stryker
I think'm way too famous! Ayden Stryker
Ever since Mesmerize r, Ayden Stryker
People keep making tons of songs featuring me and Miku! Ayden Stryker
But is something wrong with that? Ayden Stryker
Ayden The thing is..
Ayden Mi ku-Teto duets There are so many that people are getting tired of uuu ssss!
Ayden There are so many Mi ku-Teto duets that people are geting tired of uuu ssss!
They're getting tired of Ayden Str
OKAY OKAY!!! MEEEE EEEE!!! Ayden Stryker
Te to! Ayden Stryker
Nah, they probably just jealous Ayden Stryker
Jealous? Ayden Stryker
Wanna calling bet that the ones your songs s with Miku "'slop'
- -` Ayden St ker
Ayden S Stryker... Are your r old colleagues?
My old colleagues.? Ayden Sty ker
Def oko! office mm UTAU INFORMATION のはインターンを おりください
You're hating songs!? on my s AV de
Of course I am A de ker
It's not fair that you became so successful when you started out just like me
UT AU You even appeared I in Miku Concert! a len
But Def oko! Ayden
Spreading hate isn't 3 the solution! Av den
What we should do is be 2 happy that our friends have come so far
Instead of hating them
office m UTAU  NFORMATON Ayden Stryker
office mm UTA U  NFORMATON Ay Screw that, another Mi ku Teto slop just dropped
office mm UTAU IH FORMATION Ayden Stn gonna hate it